jobpot.net 2011-09-04

# Jobpot.net Privacy Policy

Jobpot Privacy Policy for our web site www.Jobpot.net:

At Jobpot (Jobpot.net or "us"), we know you are concerned about your privacy, so we developed this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and disclose your Personal Information. As a guiding principal, our mission at Jobpot.net is to make a better job marketplace. That means we take an abundance of time researching and connecting with the best online businesses and employers around.  This site doesn't require that you give any personal information to utilize the site to apply for positions. This site is made up of thousands of employers and and millions of job oppurtunities.  In short this site is a search engine for employment, partnered by [Simplyhired](http://www.simplyhired.com/). If you want to link to us or advertise with us.  

By using this site (the **“Site”** ) or any other site that is operated by Jobpot.net, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information you agree that you are consenting to our use and disclosure of the information that you provide, and consenting to receive emails, as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Jobpot.net Terms of Service. If a term is capitalized and not defined in this Privacy Policy, it is defined in the Terms of Service.  For any additional clarification please contact us. 

**Provided Information:** All information provided to you is based off of opinion, gathered by our research staff. All opinions are formed off of the latest statistical results and professional literature from top researchers in the United states. The information provided to you should be used as a tool and or recommendation for increased performance when put in the different scenarios mentioned through out the site. Jobpot.net offers no guarantees for any of the provided information. Jobs are posted based off of an affiliate Database supplied by thousands of employers. Updates are first addressed by the employers and then updated by our affiliates.   

So we are clear about the terminology we are using, when we use the phrase **“Personal Information”** in this Privacy Policy, we mean information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. When we use the phrase **“Non-Personal Information”** in this Privacy Policy, we mean information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Non-Personal Information does not enable identification of or contact with, individual persons.   

How We Collect Information:  
We receive and store information you give us (either through the Site orin any way you may choose, as part of the services available on the Site (the **“Services”** ) Service, to enter Personal Information, including your name, street address, email address, and phone number. When you create your match profile on the Site, we collect categories of information relevant to your profile, including your contact information, information about your experience, education, and desired salary limitations. When you submit a resume to one of the employers featured on this site you must refer to that employers privacy policy for information about there procedures. 

“ **Cookies** ” are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

How We Use Information   
By using the Site, should you provide any contact information, rest assured it is held in the highest of confidence and will only be used in the respect that it was provided.  Jobpot.net will virtually only contact you in response to inquiries or business communications. From time-to-time, we may create Non-Personal Information from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name and other contact information) that would personally identify you. Generally, we use this Non-Personal Information in statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of our Services. We reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information in our discretion.   

**Disclosure of Information**  
We are not responsible for disclosing your Personal Information to our employers who may have postings for job openings (“employers”). We do not control how employers use or disclose information they obtain from us, Including Personal Information, and those employers may also share your Personal Information with other employers that may have job openings. If you do not want to allow your Disclosed Profile (as defined below) to be shared with other employers, you may opt out of this feature by not applying. Otherwise, we enable employers to share interesting profiles with other employers. Also, if you have come to our Site by following a link from one of our affiliates or business partners or by following a link in an online job posting from a potential employer, they may use the information consistent with their privacy policy instead of this Privacy Policy. Since we do not control how they may use your information, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  

**Disclosure of Information**  
In addition, if provided we may disclose your Personal Information:

(a) if such disclosure is made to comply with the law or an order issued by a court or an authorized administrative agency, respond to a subpoena, protect the rights or property of hinesvillejobs or its affiliated companies, prevent a crime, or protect the personal safety or rights of others;

(b) to our service providers for the purpose of providing services on our behalf, such as customer service, information technology services, and hosting services;

(c) as part of a merger or consolidation, or part of the sale of all or substantially all the stock or assets of the business to which the information pertains.

(d) as part of a disposition in a bankruptcy proceeding in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court.   
Please be aware that when you voluntarily display or distribute Personal Information on the Site or in other ways, that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. We cannot be responsible for Personal Information you voluntarily display, disclose or distribute on the Site or in any other way. 

**How to Mask Your Identity**   
Giving you tools to help you protect your contact information is a vital part of our mission. The Services provide you the option to mask your identity from employers by choosing an alias for your Disclosed Profile and generalizing other potentially identifying information that you have provided to us or our listed employers. If you do not want an employer or the public to know your identity, you must choose an alias and you must separately pseudonym your resume before submitting it to an employer.

You need to be careful, because your resume or other information you provide to us/employer may reveal your identity. It is up to you to make sure your alias and the information you provide to us/employer truly masks your identity. Jobpot.net does not have any obligation to modify: (1) potentially identifying information in your Disclosed Profile, or (2) your resume to remove or mask information that may identify you. Your **“Disclosed Profile”** means your Personal Information that us/employer may disclose to an employer (including your resume) according to the information that you provide. 

**  
Employers Use of Your Disclosed Profile**   
**_Note:_ that Jobpot.net does not have any control over how an employer uses and discloses your Personal Information, including information you provide directly to that employer. You acknowledge and agree that (1) Jobpot.ne does not evaluate any employer’s privacy practices, and (2) Jobpot.ne will not have any liability for any actions of any employer.** You should know that employers to whom we may disclose your Disclosed Profile may share your Disclosed Profile with others.   

**Accessing and Controlling Your Information**   
We are committed to giving you control over your Personal Information. The personal information provided is stricly voluntary but will be kept in the highest confidencet. Once an employer has your information, once again it is that employer discretion to as to how your information is being used.  Please remember, however, that if you've already disclosed some of your Personal Information, we can not access that Personal Information any longer and can not force the deletion or modification of that Personal Information by the parties to whom you have made those disclosures. 

**Partners,   Affiliates & Exterior Sites **   
Jobpot.net is not responsible for the content or upkeep of none of our affiliates, partners, or exterior links on this site. Please see the contact page for that business.  Please notify us if any derogatory, offensive or explicit information is found on this site.  We will remove the content ASAP. 

**Security**   
Jobpot.net is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. Our affiliates use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Even though we have taken steps to ensure that your Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, you should know that we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. You assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site and the information you post or access through the Site.   

**User Feedback**   
If you provide feedback, any such comments and any email we receive becomes the property of Jobpot.net.  We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our Services without paying any royalties or other compensation to you.   

**Changes**   
This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Service and informational based content. Continued use of our Service following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. All such changes will apply to previously collected information. 

**Contact Us**  
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.  
  
---
